{"tossups": [{"question": "<em>In response to the growth of this group, the</em> danka <em>system was codified.</em> Members of this group were burnt in straw raincoats after a successful siege of Hara castle. A practice in which icons called fumi-e were trampled was designed to identify members of this group. Members of this group were led by the teenager Amakusa Shiro in the Shimabara rebellion. For the point, name this once-persecuted Japanese religious group, which grew thanks to the activities of Francis Xavier and other Jesuits.", "answer": "Japanese <b><u>Christian</u></b>s [or hidden <b><u>Christian</u></b>s; or <b><u>Kirishitan</u></b>; prompt on \"Japanese people\"; prompt on \"Japanese peasants\"]  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>During the reign of Charles VI of France, several men performing this activity while dressed</em> <em>in resin-soaked rags were accidentally set on fire.</em> In a bizarre case of mass hysteria, hundreds of people compulsively performed this activity in Strasbourg during a namesake 1518 plague. A rapper sword or a longsword are sometimes used in a form of this activity known as \"morris.\" The Black Death gave rise to an artistic motif in which skeletons engage this activity. For the point, name this activity exemplified by the minuet and the waltz.", "answer": "<b><u>dancing</u></b> [or <b><u>dance</u></b>s]  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>A man with this name was advised by the pope to allow marriage outside the \"second degree\"</em> <em>in the</em> Libellus responsorium<em>.</em> One man of this name allied with Bertha, King Ethelbert's wife, and undertook a journey after Gregory I saw some angelic child slaves. A writer with this name described being admonished by his mother Monica after stealing some pears from a tree. Ambrose of Milan tutored that man of this name, who wrote <em>City of God</em> and was converted from Manichaeism. For the point, give this name shared by the first Archbishop of Canterbury and a saint from Hippo who wrote <em>Confessions</em>.", "answer": "<b><u>Augustine</u></b> [or <b><u>Augustine</u></b> of Hippo; or <b><u>Augustine</u></b> of Canterbury; or <b><u>Austin</u></b>; Aurelius <b><u>Augustinus</u></b> Hipponensis]  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>This event was inspired by sociologist Harry Edwards, the founder of the OPHR.</em> One participant in this event was ostracized due to it as well as for his opposition to the White Australia policy. After this event, <em>Time</em> Magazine called it \u201cAngrier. Nastier. Uglier\u201d and Avery Brundage expelled the two Americans involved. During the event, Peter Norman wore a human rights badge while the Gold and Bronze medal winners at the 200 meter dash had to share a pair of gloves. For the point, name this event during the 1968 Summer Olympics in which Tommie Smith and John Carlos each raised one fist.", "answer": "<b><u>Black Power</u></b> salute [prompt on \u201c1968 Summer Olympics\u201d or equivalents]", "metadata": "TR"}, {"question": "<em>This general forced Christian IV to pull Denmark out of a European war with the Treaty of</em> <em>Lubeck.</em> His faith in astrology kept him ignorant of the treachery of his officers Walter Devereux and Ottavio Piccolomini. This man\u2019s ardent opposition to the Edict of Restitution and his forced retreat at the Battle of Lutzen earned the ire of Ferdinand II, which culminated in the Holy Roman Emperor greenlighting his murder in 1634. For the point, name this great general during the Thirty Years War\u2019 whose life was dramatized in a play cycle by Friedrich Schiller.", "answer": "Albrecht von <b><u>Wallenstein</u></b> [or Albrecht Wenzel Eusebius von <b><u>Wallenstein</u></b>; or Albrecht von <b><u>Waldstein</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "AG"}, {"question": "<em>An unused New Yorker cover of this event features a man smiling ghoulishly while wearing a</em> <em>top hat and riding in a car with his predecessor</em>. During this event, a man read a Raymond Moley penned speech, noting \"the money changers have fled from their high seats in the temple.\" The primary speaker at this event had been shot at recently by Giuseppe Zangara and shortly after its completion, proposed the Emergency Banking Act. At this event, a man proclaimed \"the only thing we have to fear is...fear itself.\" For the point, name this March 4, 1933, event, the official beginning of a certain Democrat's presidency.", "answer": "<b><u>F</u></b>ranklin Delano <b><u>Roosevelt\u2019s first inauguration</u></b> or <b><u>first inaugural address</u></b> [or <b><u>FDR\u2019s first inauguration</u></b>; accept <b><u>1933 presidential inauguration</u></b> until \u201c1933\u201d is mentioned\u201d; prompt on partial answers such as <b><u>Roosevelt\u2019s first inauguration</u></b> or <b><u>Roosevelt inauguration</u></b>]", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "<em>Cotton Mather drew upon this man\u2019s defense of Anglicanism,</em> The Christian Virtuoso<em>, to write</em> <em>\u201cThe Christian Philosopher.\u201d</em> This scientist's outlook is contrasted with that of Thomas Hobbes in a book by Steven Shapin\u2019s and Simon Schaffer\u2019s.This man wrote a 1661 dialogue in which Philoponus, Themistius and others debate the nature of the title scientific discipline in the garden of Carneades (<b>pr. car-NAY-uh-deez</b>). Emile Clapeyron combined this man\u2019s law and Charles\u2019s law to derive the ideal gas law. For the point, what scientist authored <em>The Skeptical Chymist</em> and who names a law describing the volume and pressure of a gas at constant temperature?", "answer": "Robert <b><u>Boyle</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "Ike"}, {"question": "<em>Roberto Viaux (<b>pr. vee-OH</b>) headed a group in one attempt to overthrow this man, codenamed</em> <em>FUBELT.</em> This leader put Stafford Beer in charge of a computer-run system to manage the economy that was named Project Cybersyn<em>.</em> The Tanquetazo was a failed attempt to overthrow this leader. This leader was elected as the head of the Popular Unity coalition, and won support after the death of Rene Schneider. In 2011, an autopsy declared this man to have committed suicide with an AK-47 given by Fidel Castro after his military stormed La Moneda. For the point, name this socialist President of Chile who was ousted in a 1973 coup and succeeded by Augusto Pinochet.", "answer": "Salvador <b><u>Allende</u></b> Gossens  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em>This song was written to replace \u201cSepia Panorama\u201d in its ensemble\u2019s setlist.</em> Performers of the trumpet solo in this work almost always copy the Ray Nance original rather than improvise one of their own. Its most famous lyrics were written by Joya Sherrill, and say how the title action is the best way \u201cto go to Sugar Hill.\u201d This work\u2019s title route runs from Bedford-Stuyvesant to New York\u2019s center of African-American culture, Harlem. For the point, what Billy Strayhorn composition about a subway line became the signature song for Duke Ellington\u2019s orchestra?", "answer": "\u201c<b><u>Take the A Train</u></b>\u201d  {II}", "metadata": "CW"}, {"question": "<em>Troops loyal to this leader threw the corpses of fleeing Istrians into sinkholes called foibe.</em> A movement known as MASPOK opposed this man, who used the Goli Otok prison for political dissidents. As a military leader, he was targeted in Operation Rosselsprung and fought against the Chetniks. This dictator's country underwent the Informbiro period after he split with Stalin, leading him to help found the Non-Aligned Movement. For the point, name this leader of the Partisans who became the communist dictator of Yugoslavia.", "answer": "Josip Broz <b><u>Tito</u></b> [or Marshall <b><u>Tito</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>While teaching at this school, Robert Fogel co-wrote a book controversially claiming that</em> <em>some slaves benefited from slavery, called \u201cTime on the Cross</em>.\u201d One professor at this university argued that it is difficult to predict the impact of an economic policy based solely on historic data, known as the Lucas Critique. A group of advisors to former Chilean President Augusto Pinochet were known as the \u201cboys\u201d from this school. The theory of monetarism originated with a professor at this school, a critic of Keynesian economics named Milton Friedman. For the point, which Midwestern university is known for its free market school of economics?", "answer": "University of <b><u>Chicago</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "BA"}, {"question": "<em>King Albert of Sweden gave Gotland to these people so that the Victual Brothers would be</em> <em>eliminated</em>. A Landmeister commanded each national chapter of this organization, which was opposed by the Lizard Union. They lost a battle on Lake Peipus, the Battle of the Ice, to Alexander Nevsky. This group was defeated by Jogaila and Vytautas the Great at the Battle of Grunwald under the direction of Grand Master Ulrich von Jungingen while fighting a namesake war against the Polish-Lithuanian Commonwealth. For the point, name this group of knightly crusaders from Germany.", "answer": "<b><u>Teutonic</u></b> knights  {II}", "metadata": "JZ"}, {"question": "<em>This general became the commander of his country\u2019s armies after a predecessor\u2019s offensive</em> <em>on the Ladies\u2019 Walkway failed</em>. To end one mutiny, this general promised no offensives until American troops arrived. This leader used a three-colored throwing axe as his personal emblem and was accused of \u201cpessimism\u201d by Ferdinand Foch. This general who rallied his men in 1916 with the cry \u201cOn les aura!\u201d is rarely commemorated because of his tenure as the president of the Vichy regime. For the point, name this French World War I general who was the hero of Verdun.", "answer": "Philippe <b><u>Petain</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "PL"}, {"question": "<em>A resort city named for this man is connected by the Silver Strand to mainland San Diego.</em> One of this man\u2019s expeditions was accompanied by a parallel naval force led by Hernando de Alarcon. Tempted by rumors of the legendary wealth of Quivira, this man led an unsuccessful expedition to Kansas. Seeking the Seven Cities of Gold, this explorer dispatched Garcia Lopez de Cardenas, the first white man to follow the Colorado River to the Grand Canyon. For the point, name this Spanish governor who explored the American southwest.", "answer": "Francisco Vazquez de <b><u>Coronado</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "EA"}, {"question": "<em>A leader of this place formulated three R's for it, including research and reform.</em> An art school was established in this place by painter Enella Benedict. Residents of this place could live in a camp in Bowen Park during the summer. This place was initially co-run by Ellen Gates Starr and was based on Toynbee Hall in London. This institution was located in \"Little Italy,\" and it provided kindergarten for the children of immigrant sweatshop workers. For the point, name this settlement house operated in Chicago by Jane Addams.", "answer": "<b><u>Hull House</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>The Earl of Derby resigned as Colonial Secretary for the second time because of his support</em> <em>for these laws.</em> Charles Villiers organized the publishing of a \u201cBlue Book\u201d opposed to these acts, and a petition was presented against these documents by Thomas Tooke. They began to operate under a sliding scale during the ministry of the Duke of Wellington. <em>The Economist</em> was founded by James Wilson to coordinate resistance to these acts, and Richard Cobden led a namesake league opposed to them. They were finally repealed by Robert Peel. For the point, name these laws which put high tariffs on a certain grain.", "answer": "<b><u>Corn Laws</u></b> [or <b><u>Importation Act, 1815</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "JZ"}, {"question": "<em>This person released a hare from a robe in order to win the favor of the goddess Andraste.</em> While an opposing army was busy massacring priests on the Isle of Mona, this leader sacked the city of Camulodunum. This leader allied with the Trinovantes but was defeated by Suetonius Paulinus at the Battle of Watling Street. This person succeeded Prasutagus as the leader of the Iceni tribe and may have been inspired by to act by her public flogging and the rape of her daughters. For the point, name this woman who led a revolt against the Romans in Britain.", "answer": "<b><u>Boudica</u></b> [or <b><u>Boadicea</u></b>; or <b><u>Buddug</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>A proof of one of this mathematician\u2019s theorems makes use of the Gorenstein Property</em>. This man developed the method of \u201cinfinite descent\u201d to prove his namesake right triangle theorem. A theorem named for this man was proven when a man used the Taniyama-Shimura conjecture to relate elliptic curves to modular forms. Andrew Wiles proved that theorem named for this man three hundred years after his death, which concerns the integer solvability of a three term equation. For the point, name this French mathematician, with a \u201clast theorem\u201d that took centuries to solve.", "answer": "Pierre de <b><u>Fermat</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "Ike"}, {"question": "<em>This event celebrated Joshua Slocum\u2019s circumnavigation of the globe on the ship Spray three</em> <em>years earlier.</em> An attraction at this event, known as <em>A Trip to the Moon</em>, later became the keystone at Luna Park in Coney Island. A nearby X-ray machine was left unused during the most famous occurrence at this event, which happened inside the Temple of Music. During this event, alternating current brought electricity from Niagara Falls forty miles away, and powered the electric chair that eventually executed the anarchist Leon Czolgosz (<b>pr. CHOLE-goash</b>) for his actions here. For the point, name this 1901 World\u2019s Fair in Buffalo, where William McKinley was assassinated.", "answer": "<b><u>Pan-American Exposition</u></b> [accept <b><u>Buffalo World\u2019s Fair</u></b> or <b><u>1901 World\u2019s Fair</u> </b>before mention; prompt on the <b><u>assassination</u></b> of William <b><u>McKinley</u></b> and similar answers]", "metadata": "AG"}, {"question": "<em>A novel named for this man features a mystical bull-calf formula and fictionalizes many of</em> <em>the ideas found in its author\u2019s The White Goddess.</em> Agabus the Decapolitan narrates a historical novel in which this man\u2019s right to the throne is usurped; in that novel by Robert Graves, he is a king. This character states \u201cIt is accomplished\u201d at the end of another historical novel in which he hallucinates living an idyllic life. A novel by Nikos Kazantzakis that is titled for his \u201cLast Temptation\u201d was adapted into a film by Martin Scorsese. For the point, name this historical figure, the son of God.", "answer": "<b><u>Jesus</u><u>Christ</u></b> [accept either]  {II}", "metadata": "Ike"}, {"question": "<em>This man was criticized by his people for his alliance with Francis, Duke of Anjou which</em> <em>ended when Anjou\u2019s forces were massacred in an attempt to conquer Antwerp</em>. In a speech to the Council of State, this man spoke in favor of religious freedom. This man gained his nickname after a conversation with Henry II of France when he pretended to know about a secret agreement to exterminate Protestantism. This man was assassinated by Spanish sympathizer Balthasar Gerard after being declared an outlaw by Philip II. For the point, which Prince of Orange was the first leader of the Dutch Revolt?", "answer": "<b><u>William I</u></b> of Orange [or <b><u>William the Silent</u></b>; prompt on <b><u>William of Orange</u></b> and partial answers such as <b><u>William</u></b>;]  {II}", "metadata": "TR"}, {"question": "<em>This artist painted an Anglo-Dutch naval victory in the Nine Years\u2019 War in \u201cThe Battle of La</em> <em>Hogue</em>\u201d<em>.</em> A white robed Roman widow bears the ashes of her assassinated husband Germanicus in this artist\u2019s <em>Agrippina Landing at Brundisium</em>. He became the first American-born president of the Royal Academy after succeeding Joshua Reynolds. He controversially depicted Simon Fraser and other onlookers wearing contemporary dress in a painting which shows the aftermath of a battle on the Plains of Abraham. For the point, name this painter of <em>The Death of General Wolfe</em>.", "answer": "Benjamin <b><u>West</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "EA"}, {"question": "<em>The plaintiff in this case underwent plastic surgery and changed his name to Clyde Sarah</em>. This case's plaintiff had been recently fired as a welder and had been denied admission into the service because of ulcers. Frank Murphy's dissent in this case noted \"all residents of this nation are kin\" and denounced the \"the ugly abyss\" of discrimination on display. This case supported Executive Order 9066 and the need for \"proper security measures\" on the West Coast. For the point, name this 1944 Supreme Court case that upheld Japanese American internment.", "answer": "<em><b><u>Korematsu</u></b> v. United States</em> [or <em>United States v.</em> <em><b><u>Korematsu</u></b></em>]  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>The industry producing this product was the focus of the 2008 documentary \u201cThe Burning</em> <em>Season\u201d</em>. The burning of peat bogs to make way for producing this product has led to an annual haze over Singapore. A \"roundtable\" on this resource states that as a result of its production, Malaysia absorbs more carbon dioxide than it produces. The production of this resource threatens the habitats of the orangutan and the Sumatran tiger, and is responsible for massive deforestation in Indonesia. For the point, name this cooking ingredient gathered from a type of tropical tree.", "answer": "<b><u>palm oil</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "KG"}, {"question": "<em>During one scene in this series, George Luz tricks his superior into cutting a fence by</em> <em>pretending to be Oliver Horton</em>. In this series, the main characters train by running \u201cthree miles up, three miles down\u201d Currahee Mountain, which names the first episode in this series. Herbert Sobel and Richard Winters are characters in this series that follows the title group through D-Day, Carentan, Market Garden, and the Bulge as they serve with the 101st Division. For the point, name this HBO miniseries based on a Stephen Ambrose series about the men of Easy Company.", "answer": "<em><b><u>Band of Brothers</u></b></em> [prompt on <b><u>B.O.B</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "PL"}, {"question": "<em>These people were the first to develop a burial coffin called the larnax.</em> These people created a type of pottery known as Kamares (<b>pr. kah-MAH-race</b>) ware. The chronology of these people is divided into sections based on either their pottery or palace construction. These people were devastated by the Thera eruption. Many artworks created by this people depict bull-leaping, including a large fresco. The Phaistos Disc is a relic of these people, who developed the Linear A script. This civilization was studied by Arthur Evans, who led an excavation of Knossos. For the point, what Ancient Greek civilization was centered on Crete?", "answer": "<b><u>Minoan</u></b>s [or <b><u>Minoan</u></b> civilization]  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em>Shortly before the Declaration of Independence was signed, this state was the site of the</em> <em>Battle of Sullivan\u2019s Island.</em> This state was home to the guerilla bands of Andrew Pickens. In this state, the site of the siege of Ninety Six, a Loyalist militia was surrounded and defeated at Kings Mountain, and Cornwallis defeated Horatio Gates at Camden. This state was where Daniel Morgan defeated Banastre Tarleton at Cowpens, and where the \u201cSwamp Fox\u201d Francis Marion operated. For the point, name this state where the port of Charleston was besieged.", "answer": "<b><u>South Carolina</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em>This leader divided his state into provinces called teklay ghizats.</em> This man\u2019s realm was invaded after being blamed for a crisis at Welwel. He was targeted by a failed coup led by the Neway brothers, and sent the Kagnew Battalion to fight in the Korean War. This man assumed the title of <em>negus</em> after being named regent to Zauditu, daughter of Menelik II. In a speech before the League of Nations, he warned that \u201cIt is us today. It will be you tomorrow\u201d after Italy\u2019s invasion of his country. For the point, name this emperor of Ethiopia revered by Rastafarians.", "answer": "<b><u>Haile Selassie</u></b> I [accept Ras <b><u>Tafari</u></b> Makonnen before \u201cRastafarians\u201d]  {II}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em>Planning for this event began after a leader met with Anastas Mikoyan to secure a loan.</em> Eleanor Roosevelt\u2019s Tractors for Freedom Committee sought to free those captured during this event. This action began with landings on Playa Giron and Playa Largas, and it prompted the resignation of Allen Dulles. Participants in this event were led by Jos\u00e9 P\u00e9rez San Rom\u00e1n and known as Brigade 2506; they were trained by the CIA in Guatemala. For the point, name this failed invasion by U.S.-backed rebels in Cuba.", "answer": "<b><u>Bay of Pigs</u></b> invasion [accept Operation <b><u>Pluto</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em>An early empire of this name ultimately reduced the Mittani kingdom to vassal status.</em> Adad-Nirari II, named partly for a smith god, started an expansionary phase of this empire in the 800s BC. They're not Chaldeans, but the name of this ancient empire also identifies a still-extant Nestorian Church of the East. A prominent library was built in its capital by its emperor Ashurbanipal. About a century before the Babylonian captivity, these people besieged Jerusalem under Sennacherib. For the point, name this ancient Near Eastern empire centered at Nineveh.", "answer": "<b><u>Assyria</u></b>n empire [do not accept or prompt on \"neo-Assyrian\" or \u201cSyria\u201d]  {II}", "metadata": "MJ"}, {"question": "<em>This man\u2019s administration signed the Shufeldt Treaty with Korea.</em> William Chandler, constructed dozens of ironclads and started the Naval War College. While serving as New York\u2019s quartermaster general during the Civil War, this man befriended Roscoe Conkling<em>.</em> His navy secretary, This president vetoed the Chinese Exclusion Act and signed the Pendleton Civil Service Reform Act, the latter due in part to his predecessor\u2019s assassination by \u201cdisappointed office-seeker\u201d Charles Guiteau (<b>pr. ghee-TOE</b>). For the point, name this president who succeeded James Garfield.", "answer": "Chester Alan <b><u>Arthur</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em>In this year, NASA released the famous \"Face on Mars\" photo taken by the Viking 1 lander</em>. In July of this year, an American Legion convention in Philadelphia was marred by an outbreak of what could be named Legionnaires' disease. In televised presidential debates during this year, the first since Kennedy/Nixon, the incumbent inaccurately said \"there is no Soviet domination of Eastern Europe.\" That incumbent lost the election this year thanks to his pardon of Richard Nixon. For the point, name this year, when America celebrated its bicentennial.", "answer": "<b><u>1976</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>In the 1990s, these people formed the Inkatha Freedom Party.</em> A 1964 film named for these people introduced Michael Caine in his first major role. In the early 19th century, these people joined with the neighboring Nguni, to fight a neighboring tribe. One chief of these people, who lost the Battle of Blood River, was Dingane (<b>pr. din-GAH-nay</b>). Another leader of these people fought a series of roads called the Mfecane, (<b>pr. umf-CAH-nay</b>) or \u201cCrushing,\u201d and organized his <em>impi</em> regiments into a formation called \u201cbuffalo horns.\u201d That chief was Shaka. For the point, name this south African tribe that fought a series of 19th-century wars with the British.", "answer": "<b><u>Zulu</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em>A monarch of this name declared the right of every traveler to \"lie down to sleep by the</em> <em>roadside without fear of harm\".</em> Isaac Davis and John Young traded guns and cannons to the first king of this name, which literally means \"the very lonely man\" or \"the man set apart.\" Christianity replaced a system of sacred law called <em>kapu</em> under the second monarch of this name, whose first holder secured hospitality with the Law of the Splintered Paddle. A man with this name won the Battle of the Leaping Mullet Fish to secure control of the archipelago where James Cook was murdered. For the point, give the regnal name of the first five kings of Hawai'i.", "answer": "<b><u>Kamehameha</u></b> [or <b><u>Kamehameha</u></b> I; or <b><u>Kamehameha</u></b> II]  {III}", "metadata": "MJ"}, {"question": "<em>Union scouts and Virginian militia clashed around one of these places in Fairfax in the first</em> <em>land skirmish of the Civil War.</em> A battle named for one of these buildings featured intense fighting at \"Bloody Angle\" near the Mule Shoe and followed the Battle of the Wilderness in the Overland Campaign. The Battle of Spotsylvania is named for one of these buildings, as is an engagement which was followed by a meeting at Wilmer McLean's house. For the point, Robert E. Lee surrendered to Ulysses S. Grant following a battle near what sort of building in Appomattox?", "answer": "<b><u>court house</u></b>s  {II}  <b>Extra Tossup \u2013 ONLY READ IF A QUESTION IS BOTCHED!</b> <em>The opening piece of this work is sometimes published with an added \u201cSchwencke measure.\u201d</em> Twentieth-century imitations of this work include Dmitry Shostakovich\u2019s Opus 87 and Paul Hindemith\u2019s <em>Ludus Tonalis.</em> Its opening piece\u2019s 35 measures mostly consist of rising arpeggios in C major, and it was written to promote a system which, unlike meantone, could modulate across the entire circle of fifths. For the point, what collection of keyboard works by Johann Sebastian Bach, followed by a similar Book 2, features a prelude and fugue in every major and minor key?  ANSWER: <em>The</em> <em><b><u>Well-Tempered Clavier</u></b>, Book 1</em> [or <em>Das</em> <em><b><u>Wohltemperierte Klavier</u></b></em>]  {II}", "metadata": "JB"}], "bonuses": []}